<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Records &#8211; Ephemeral</title>
	<atom:link href="/category/records/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description>There is no memory left.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 16:23:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.6.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Memory Record: Subject A32-09</title>
		<link>/2024/08/31/memory-record-subject-a32-09/</link>
					<comments>/2024/08/31/memory-record-subject-a32-09/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[trashpanda]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 16:18:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Records]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=16</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Maria Velasquez: *&#8221;I’ve been carrying this weight for years, and it’s only getting heavier. I remember the first time I found out I was pregnant—it felt like the universe had granted me my greatest wish. It wasn’t just happiness; it was pure, unfiltered joy. I could see our future together so clearly—her tiny hands wrapping [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><em>Maria Velasquez:</em></p>



<p>*&#8221;I’ve been carrying this weight for years, and it’s only getting heavier. I remember the first time I found out I was pregnant—it felt like the universe had granted me my greatest wish. It wasn’t just happiness; it was pure, unfiltered joy. I could see our future together so clearly—her tiny hands wrapping around my finger, her first words bringing tears to my eyes, her laughter filling every corner of our home. I envisioned her growing up, her first day of school, teaching her to ride a bike, watching her blossom into the person she was meant to be. But that joy&#8230; it was ripped away from me so suddenly, so violently, that it left a void I’ve never been able to fill.</p>



<p>The miscarriage&#8230; it shattered everything. One moment I was filled with hope and anticipation, and the next, I was drowning in despair. It wasn’t just the loss of a child; it was the loss of an entire future, a lifetime of memories that would never come to be. Every time I close my eyes, I see her—not as she was, but as she could have been. I see the life we could have had, the daughter I should have been holding in my arms, the love I should have been nurturing. But instead, all I’m left with is this emptiness, this unbearable pain that refuses to fade.</p>



<p>I thought time would heal this wound, that eventually, the pain would soften into something bearable. But it hasn’t. If anything, it’s only grown, festering like an open wound that won’t close. It’s like a shadow that darkens every part of my life, following me everywhere I go. I can’t look at a child without feeling a deep, hollow ache in my chest, a reminder of what I lost. I can’t walk past a playground without breaking down, imagining her laughter among the others, knowing I’ll never hear it. I want to remember her as she was in my dreams, as the child I loved before she was even born, but all I feel is the loss, the emptiness that she left behind.</p>



<p>I can’t keep living like this. I can’t keep waking up every day with this crushing sadness, this overwhelming sense of loss that never goes away. I just want to forget the pain, the dreams, the plans we made for a future that never came. I want to be able to breathe again, to wake up without this weight on my chest, to smile without feeling guilty for moving on. I want to be able to live my life without this constant reminder of what could have been. Please, help me forget&#8230; help me forget this pain, so I can finally move forward, so I can finally start living again.&#8221;*</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2024/08/31/memory-record-subject-a32-09/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
